(Blonde girl(arriving):)Hello?
(Penny(exiting apartment):)Oh, hey.
Hi. I just wanted to bring you
a housewarming gift.
(Alicia:)That is so sweet.
(Alicia:)- Come on in. Let's open it.
- Great.
- Nice dress.
- Oh, this? I'm dressed like a slob today.
(Alicia:)The guys have been helping me
set up my sound system.
(Alicia:)I've never had
such good-looking technical support.
Oh, pish posh.
[INAUDIBLE]
(Howard:)I don't know. It means shucks.
(Howard:)Shucks means shucks.
Let one go once in a while.
(Sheldon:)Penny,
you wanna hear something awesome?
(Penny:)- Yeah.
- Alicia is an actress just like you.
(Penny:)That is so awesome.
- Well, trying to be, but it's so hard.
- I know, tell me about it.
I've been here three months.
All I've gotten is a couple commercials.
(Alicia:)And this recurring thing on a soap.